{
    "id": "89227bef709c4a20a50dff2757d308cd",
    "title": "Most vs. The Most",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are ……………………….. generous woman I have ever met.",
            "description": "Here we use most to make the superlative form of beautiful. The is also used before superlative adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "the most",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. children love watching cartoons.",
            "description": "When most is used as a determiner, it does not take the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………….. students hate mathematics.",
            "description": "When most is used as a determiner, it does not take the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is ………………………………… beautiful girl in the class?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… of my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "When most is a determiner, it does not take the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… of us wanted him to win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country consumes ……………………………….. meat?",
            "description": "When most has a superlative meaning, it is normally used with the.",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. children believe in fairies.",
            "description": "When most simply means ‘the majority of’, it is not used with ‘the’.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. of us want to get rid of corruption.",
            "description": "When most simply means ‘the majority of’, it is not used with ‘the’.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… criminals are non-violent.",
            "description": "When most is a determiner, it is used without the. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She wasn’t as beautiful as the others, but she was …………………………….. intelligent.",
            "description": "Here we use most to make the superlative form of beautiful. The is also used before superlative adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Thank you for ……………………………….. unforgettable evening.",
            "description": "When most means very it is not used with the.",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most",
                "a most"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}